[Music]
[Música]
Don't be afraid of Oh look, a hater said to
no tema de Ay mira un hater ha dicho
burn them and Argo are twin brothers, I
quemarlos y y argo son hermanos gemelos
mean this is tremendous eh the issue of
o sea esto es tremendo eh el tema de los
haters, the issue of haters is tremendous
haters el tema de los haters es tremendo
eh today we're going to see here a few
eh hoy vamos a ver aquí unas cuantas de
things that haters have with uncle
movidas que tienen los hater con el tío
Shur and Gibel and others, if I left something
shur y gibel y demás no si me dejo algo
behind, let me know We also have
por atrás hacérmelo saber También
a goal today that's going to
tenemos un objetivo hoy que os va a
motivate you eh it's going to motivate you not to
motivar eh os va a motivar a que no
donate a cent today the goal of Super
donis un pavo hoy el objetivo de Super
chat is a button against Javi el peluca
chat es un botón contra Javi el peluca
el peluca This is a guy, eh I
el peluca Este es un chico Eh me he
went into his Twitter account, I mean, eh
metido en su cuenta de Twitter o sea eh
more than anything to put you
más que nada para para poneros un poco
in context, okay because this is a guy
en contexto vale porque este es un chico
who made the following video and the
que ha hecho el siguiente vídeo y los
haters are applauding him because he
haters lo están aplaudiendo porque ha
made the following video and that Argos and
hecho el siguiente vídeo y que Argos y
Marlos are brothers, I don't know if he was
marlos son hermano no sé si estaba
talking about Argos and Marlos or their
hablando de Argos y marlos o de sus
parents, okay, but he said it, okay, I mean,
padres vale pero lo ha dicho vale o sea
this video is being shared, well,
Este vídeo lo están compartiendo pues
look at all these people, okay This
pues miad toda esta gente vale Este
video  they're sharing it like the
vídeo lo están compartiendo como el
brutal video that this kid made
vídeo brutal que ha hecho este chaval
okay, I mean, they don't care what it is eh
vale o sea les vale lo que sea eh
Wait a
Espérate un
minute Well of course I went to see
momento Pues claro yo me he metido a ver
who he is or what he was doing I went to see
quién es o qué hacía me he metido a ver
where this
que que de dónde había salido este
man came from Okay and it turns out that by going
hombre Vale y resulta ser que metiéndome
into his account the twists towards me are How
en su cuenta los twists hacia mí son Qué
old is he grandpa are you [ __ ] These
edad tiene abuelo eres subnormal Estos
are in response to me okay love yourself a
son en respuesta a mí vale quiérete un
little here me asking Editors and he says do you
poco aquí yo pidiendo Editores y dice
prefer them Latinos too right
los prefieres latinos también verdad
like your master I say facto this eh facto is
como tu amo Digo facto esto eh facto es
eh m that Ricky was right and I wasn't about
eh m que Ricky tenía la razón y yo no en
the strikes okay because when
el tema de los strike vale porque cuando
he puts them in it's okay because he or I mean
él los mete está bien porque a él o sea
when they call a strike on him they're not right
cuando a él le ponen strike no están
because Ricky has
bien porque a Ricky no le han tirado
never had a video thrown at him and they've thrown it at me
nunca un vídeo y a mí me le han tirado
you see the difference and the trend is this
ves la diferencia e la tónica es esta
okay the thing about Javi Oliveira's fans is
vale lo de los fans de Javi oliveira es
scary it's pissed off good challenge lo
acojonante está picado buen reto lo
lailo no no no don't support that challenge it
lailo no no no no apoyéis ese reto que
's against Javil Pelucas eh em from here I
es contra javil pelucas eh em desde aquí
publicly apologize to  csita and to
pido perdón públicamente a csita y a
jabi oliveira I made slander and
jabi oliveira hice calumnias y
inappropriate comments which I
comentarios fuera de lugar de los cuales
regret Ah I mean woof woof I mean
me arrepiento Ah o sea guau guau o sea
the guy Mira woof woof said the puppy I
el tío Mira guau guau dijo el perrito O
mean the guy Mira was laughing at the
sea el tipo Mira se reía de lo de las
conversations of miar that
conversaciones de miar las que publicó
Win michu published but he was laughing at her not at
Win michu pero se reía de ella no de de
the I mean the guy was like on
las o sea el tío estaba como de parte
my behalf trying to get closer to me so I would pay
mía intentaba como acercarse que le
attention to him then for a while he
diera bola luego durante una época me
insulted me with the puppy thing I don't know what I don't
insultaba con lo de perrito No sé qué no
know how much and then finally he
sé cuánto y luego pues finalmente me me
apologized as if I had
pidió perdón como si yo me Hubiera
found out what the [ __ ] he had
enterado de lo que [__] me hubiera
said to me God knows what it was and
dicho vete tú a saber lo que sería y ya
then again no eem how I don't how I didn't pay attention to him well he
luego otra vez no eem como no le como no
acquired the role of
le hice caso pues adquirió el papel otra
puppy again and those things no let's see
vez de perrito y esas cosas no a ver
but well the level is this and that Argos
pero bueno el nivel es este y que Argos
yarlo are brothers Why do I say this and
yarlo son herman Por qué digo esto y por
why am I supporting this because I have been able to
qué estoy apoyando este porque he podido
get more than one proof I have
conseguir más que una prueba he
gotten several Although it is and that argo
conseguido varias Aunque es y que argo
yarlo are brothers he has gotten many
yarlo son hermano ha conseguido muchas
proofs okay I will repeat it again there I say
pruebas vale lo repetiré otra vez ahí
that they are brothers belonging to
digo que son hermanos pertenecientes a
the same litter  if you don't have the
la misma camada si no te dan las
brainpower to think without being a
neuronas para pensar sin hacértela
gossip it's not my fault your mom is
chismosa no es culpa mía tu mamá está
very hot Javi in ​​the Sur video the
muy buena Javi en el vídeo de Sur la
serl gives me the role of my life in the
serl me da la pape de mi vida en los
first 2 minutes Sur is calculating
primeros 2 minutos Sur está calculando
the amount of tweets that El pelucas
la cantidad de tweets que El pelucas te
dedicated to you and Dallas Haha In case you
dedicó a ti y a Dallas Jaja Por si lo
want to see it
quieres ver
[Music]
[Música]
eh it's that it's 44 minutes Ah the first
eh es que son 44 minutos Ah los primeros
2 minutes okay I'm putting it here so when
2 minutos vale Lo pongo aquí para cuando
we get to javiel peluca it's that they are
lleguemos a javiel peluca es que son
all haters today they are all haters This
todos hater hoy son todos hater Este
first excerpt are all haters no I mean
primer extracto son todos hater no O sea
here we see the shur who is fighting
aquí vemos al shur que se está peleando
with laser len or in other words the herlen I
con laser len o sea las herlen yo lo de
don't really understand what this man is about I mean I do
este hombre no lo entiendo de verdad o
n't know if it's because I already said it
sea es que no sé si es porque ya lo dije
yesterday no also no I mean the things he's
ayer no también no o sea las cosas que
doing today I saw him calling
está haciendo hoy lo he visto llamando
Dallas an abuser again I mean but an
otra vez a Dallas maltratador o sea pero
abuser psychological abuser
maltratador maltratador psicológico
animal abuser also a groomer
maltratador de animales también groomer
and all these things I don't understand it I mean I'm
y todas estas cosas no lo entiendo o sea
really trying to understand it eh I mean
de verdad lo intento entender eh o sea
I want to think [ __ ] what  he's
quiero pensar [__] que se está
lining his pockets he earns 200 bucks because he says
forrando gana 200 pavos porque él dice
he does it for money No in fact we have
que lo hace por dinero No de hecho hemos
filed several lawsuits in
presentado en las demandas varios cli en
which he claims he does it for money
las que él afirma que lo hace por dinero
but of course I understand that when he says he
pero claro entiendo que cuando él dice
does it for money it's because His
que lo hace por dinero es porque Su
content is literally This is worth it he
contenido es literalmente Esto vale él
tries to make a video about any other
intenta hacer un vídeo de cualquier otro
topic 500 views Okay and he starts
tema 500 visitas Vale y se pone a
defaming me and Dala and there are 5000
difamar me a mí y a dala y son 5000
we're talking about 4 I don't know 4 3
estamos hablando de 4 no sé 4 3 alguna
something like that no [ __ ] you look at you eh 700
cosa así no [__] fíjate tú eh 700
views eh 1000 with the plus thing anyway
visitas eh 1000 con lo de los más en fin
Of course I understand that when he says he
Claro entiendo que cuando él dice que lo
does it for money it's that I don't know it's like
hace por dinero es eso no sé es como
someone eh who is frustrated because he didn't
alguien eh que sea frustrado porque no
want to be a youtuber for no reason he
le quería ser youtuber por huevo él
tried eh to be my editor he asked me to be my
intentó eh ser mi editor me pidió ser mi
editor and tried to be a fan of mine then he
editor e intentó ser fan mío luego se
went to write to Dallas privately
fue a escribirle a Dallas por privado
please I have defended you Look at my video I
por favor te he defendido Mira mi vídeo
don't know what no And of course he has gotten
no sé qué no Y como no pues se ha metido
into this what this
en este lo que lo que acaba de hacer el
kid that we have seen just did or rather
chaval este que hemos visto o sea sin
no but now  it's gone it's not like it's that
más No pero ya se le ha ido no sea es
when level and level you have
que ya cuando nivel e nivel tienes
demands complaints that you have them
demandas denuncias que las tienes
complicated I mean I'm not going to guess
complicadas o sea yo no voy a adivinar
the future because I'm not the best at
el futuro porque no soy el mejor
making predictions about
haciendo predicciones de los temas
judicial matters but man Maria is gorgeous a
judiciales pero hombre María guapísima
kiss you know but I don't know it's not that it does
un beso sabes pero no sé no es que a mí
n't occur to me to a person who has
no se me ocurre a una persona que me
sued me to call you a disgusting [ __ ] I
tenga demandado decirle [__] asquerosa O
mean imagine that someone I mean you
sea imagínate que alguien o sea tú no
can't say everything you think not
puedes decir todo lo que piensas no
many times no but imagine any
muchas veces no pero imagínate cualquier
person who sues you and you and you raise
persona que te demande y tú y tú subas
the level disgusting [ __ ] son of a [ __ ] [ __ ]
el nivel [__] asquerosa hijo de [__]
you understand I mean it doesn't make
cabrón me entiendes O sea no tiene
sense it doesn't cross my mind I
sentido no se me pasa por la cabeza
hope he ends up on the street but I don't
Ojalá acabe en la calle pero que no lo
know I mean no I don't wish him anything bad
sé O sea yo no yo ni le deseo nada malo
or Well I mean I don't care what I
ni Bueno o sea a mí me da igual yo lo
consider is that he violates a
que lo que considero es que a vulner un
lot of things and he has to pay
montón de de cosas y que tiene que pagar
or rather without more but it's that I see it
o sea sin más sea pero es que lo veo
logic less than Dallas I mean Dallas
logiques menos que Dallas O sea que
is worse than let's go let's
Dallas es peor que vamos ao vamos a
see it but no but if I have said it I mean yes
verlo pero que no pero si yo lo he dicho
yes  suddenly I make a
O sea si si de repente yo le hago un
video or I criticize José
vídeo o yo hago una crítica a José
Bretón they defend José Bretón
bretón ellos defienden a José bretón
but if I have said that many
pero si eso lo he dicho ya en un montón
times and they were extremely outraged
de veces y se indignaron muchísimo
when I said it like no it is not literal it is
cuando lo di como no no es literal es
literal they are talking to ra but
literal se están hablando con ra pero
both he and my mother talk to each other
tanto él como la mamá de mi se hablan
with ra dude lmente he was part of pambi
con ra tío lmente era parte de pambi no
weren't you very outraged with pambi
estabais muy indignados con pambi
pending that I have already made RAE
pendiente que ya le he hecho RAE
literally the audios of RAE
literalmente los audios de de RAE
yelling at his girlfriend on the phone because he didn't
gritando la novia por teléfono porque no
answer her or come on r is a person who that no no it
la atendía o vamos r es una persona que
should not be treated as a side it
que no no se debería tratar de un bando
is not sevill betti I mean r is a
no es sevill betti o sea r es una
person who is objectively delinquent
persona que es objetivamente delincuente
and violent I mean how are you going to talk
y violenta o sea cómo te vas a hablar
to that person if he is super
con esa persona si está super
involved against abusers it makes no
involucrado contra los maltratadores no
sense it makes no sense at all
tiene sentido no tiene sentido ninguno
well let's see what is happening to the south
bueno a ver qué es lo que le pasa al sur
that they are messing with him for what
que se están metiendo con él por qué
context I was looking exactly
contexto yo estuve viendo exactamente
What is the number of tweets and what is
Cuál es la cantidad de tweets y cuál es
the number of Okay yes of twits that
la cantidad de Bueno sí de twits que
javel peluca puts Ah okay this is [ __ ]
pone javel peluca Ah vale que esto es
This is the click that you gave me
[__] Este es el click que me habéis
said wait I'm going to leave it here
dicho espérate lo voy a dejar por aquí
because this is around here when we enter
porque esto es por aquí cuando entramos
habil peluca today here he messes with uncle
a habil peluca hoy aquí se mete con tío
shur I don't know if you remember because there was a
shur No sé si os acordáis porque hubo un
tweet from one of the haters that said
tweet de de uno de los haters que ponía
Dallas [ __ ] his sister okay
que Dallas se follaba a su hermana vale
And then uncle shur put the screenshot
Y entonces el tío shur puso la captura
as if to say damn what a [ __ ] outrage
como diciendo [__] qué [__] barbaridad
What a [ __ ] outrage I also tell you not
Qué [__] barbaridad también te digo no
specifically uncle shur okay But there are
en concreto el tío shur vale Pero hay
some of them from the chat
algunos de ellos de los de la tertulia
that have fed this type of
que han alimentado este tipo de
community and to whom it is not given to whom
comunidad y a la que a la que no le a la
the food is not given they go a
que no les da el alimento se salen un
little out of that food they go against them
poco de ese alimento se van contra ellos
meent I mean they are not healthy people a
meent o sea no son gente sana una
person who [ __ ] is that you are not
persona que coge es que no estás
criticizing Dallas for his song
criticando a Dallas por su canción
damn what the [ __ ] [ __ ] the song is no no you
[__] qué [__] [__] la canción es no
're saying already on the way well d he
no estás diciendo ya de camino pues d se
[ __ ] his sister you understand me And
[__] la hermana me entiendes Y
surely in one of the comments
seguramente en alguno de los comentarios
of the video that one of
del del vídeo que hiciera alguno de
them will say Javi dog Haha Why does
ellos pondrá Javi perro Jaja Para qué
Dallas sing a song If Javi dog
Dallas canta una canción Si Javi perro
has you understand me I mean these are things that
tiene me entiendes o sea son cosas que
they are now realizing  no for
ahora ellos se están dando cuenta no por
example now let's see what Gibel does not
ejemplo ahora vamos a ver lo de gibel no
that he is shocked by something that says jail
que se impacta de una cosa que diga jail
peluca and I have told him But then it is
peluca y le he dicho yo Pero entonces es
the least that dispatches well Well it
lo mínimo que despacha bueno Pues
turns out that uncle shur takes out the
resulta ser que el tío shur saca la
capture and says that what an outrage not
captura y dice que qué barbaridad no lo
logical what anyone would say no
lógico lo que diríamos cualquiera no
Well then lerl is criticizing uncle
Bueno pues lerl está criticando al tío
shur for having exposed that capture that
shur por haber expuesto esa captura que
is whitewashing Dallas gibel has already done
eso es blanquear a Dallas gibel ya hizo
enough cleaning in his chat Ah yeah well
bastante limpieza en su chat Ah sí pues
I'm glad man because I really don't
yo me alegro tío porque en realidad no
dislike him I mean really I don't
me cae mal o sea realmente es que no me
dislike Gibel I mean I even think he's
cae mal gibel o sea creo que incluso
funny and Karim and things it doesn't happen
tiene gracia y Karim y cosas no lo pasa
it's that he goes too far too
es que se le va muchas veces no se le va
many times Rich the critic trying to
muchas veces Rich el crítico intentando
get on the vine also I don't think
también subirse a la Parra No creo que
laser len has more visits than the
laser len tiene más visitas que el
stutterer And he is more well known and relevant
tartaja Y es más conocido y relevante
than tomy well Rich the critic and Here
que tomy bueno Rich el crítico y Aquí
the thing begins no Here the thing begins with
empieza la vaina no Aquí empieza la
Kris Chan I mean I've been
vaina de lo de kris Chan o sea He estado
looking at the case a bit superficially
mirando un poco el caso por encima
because we have never talked about Cris
porque nunca hemos hablado de lo de Cris
Chan I mean I had no [ __ ] idea about
Chan O sea no tenía ni [__] idea yo de
that case  I don't know if there was a
ese caso no sé si ha sido en algún
time when he caught us with someone else or
momento que nos ha pillado con otro o lo
whatever, no, I haven't seen him, but
que sea no no lo he visto pero por lo
apparently a guy who's been in
visto un tío que es que ha cumplido
jail. Well, if they talk to
cárcel Bueno pero si se hablan con la
Tania and support Tania, yes, they support Tania,
Tania y apoyan a la Tania si apoyan a la
what they're telling Tania
Tania que lo que le están sacando a la
is, Hey Tania, what are you
Tania es Oye Tania que es que tú estás
defending your husband? Your husband has
defendiendo a tu marido que tu marido ha
been in jail for
estado en la cárcel por estar
sleeping with a 10-year-old girl for 4 years. You
acostándose 4 años con una niña de 10
know, it's like, Well, if they talk
años sabes es como Bueno pues se hablan
to Tania, and Tania has all my support, and
con la Tania Y Tania todo mi apoyo y
Tania, a kiss, I mean, it doesn't make any
Tania un beso o sea es que no tiene
sense. Chis Chan, it's all crazy. Well, I
sentido chis Chan es todo una locura
have no idea about that case, no,
pues no tengo ni idea de ese caso no
but well, here the tosur says, exp, putting
pero bueno aquí el tosur dice exp poner
a guy who says that d went to his
a un tío que dice que d se fue a su
sister is whitewashing it, the level is
hermana es blanquearlo el nivel es
scary. Oh, there's one thing, well, Ah, but I
acojonante Ay hay una cosa bueno Ah pero
think it was in the debate, no, there's
creo que fue en el debate no que hay una
something that he said about the lawsuits, no,
cosa que le dijo sobre las demandas no
uncle shuro, it's that I've seen the clip
el tío shuro es que he visto el clip
but I don't know, a kiss Senda, but how many
pero no sé un beso Senda pero cuántas
complaints do you have? I'm going to send it, you know,
denuncias tienes voy mandar yo sabes
of course, I am, I am  a coward good and you
claro yo soy yo soy un [__] bueno y tú
a defendant dude and that's it you have to
un demandado tío y ya está hay que hay
differentiate between knowing Being brave
que diferenciar entre saber Ser valiente
and stupid mothers How many glasses does the
y estúpido madres Cuántas copas tiene el
laser have scale has donated a dó it was something
láser escala ha donado un dó era algo
about the lawsuits but it hasn't happened to me because he does
sobre las demandas pero no me ha porque
n't want to receive lawsuits Okay
no quiere recibir demandas Bueno está
okay I think you're brave laser what does it have to do with
bien me parece valiente láser qué tiene
Javi Here being a pain in the ass every
que ver Javi Aquí dando por culo todos
day not the toupee being a pain in the ass
los días no el peluquín dando por culo
every day not only because you don't want to receive complaints but also because you have this crazy guy with the toupee being a pain in the ass every day
peluquín dando por culo todos los días
not the toupee being a pain in the ass every
no el peluquín dando por culo todos los
day this is daily eh this crazy guy this guy I
días esto a diario eh el chalado este el
mean and he thinks that nothing's going to
este o sea y él cree que no le va a
happen to him this is daily eh I mean
pasar nada esto es a diario eh o sea
these types of expressions but the
este tipo de expresiones pero es que lo
worst thing is that this guy eh was like
peor es que este tipo eh estaba como
super defender super indignant that I the one
super defensor super indignado de que yo
that they condemned me because I
la de que a mí me condenaran porque le
called him crazy old woman or broom hair I don't know
dije vieja loca o pelo escoba no sé
who he is like a guy who spends all
quién es como tío que te pegas todo el
[ __ ] day insulting all day and that I
[__] día insultando todo el día y que yo
'm bothering him boy who
le estoy dando por culo a él chico que
appears in every tweet appears in every
apareces en cada tweet aparece en cada
tweet of mine  appears insulting appears today
tweet mío aparece insultando aparece hoy
appeared in one of my tweets saying
apareció en un twit mío diciendo
calling me a failure how bad the poor people
llamándome fracasado qué mal los pobres
of the discussion now they are seeing what
de la tertulia ahora están viendo lo que
you have suffered grandfather do you want these
vos has sufrido abuelo quiere vos esta
people bad propaganda 2019 does not work
gente malita propaganda 2019 no cuela Ya
They would not put up with four or
ellos no aguantarían que salgan cuatro o
five accounts coming out, yes, eh I do not give a damn
cinco cuentas yo sí eh A mí me las me la
at all that they come out they
pela por completo que salgan me parecen
even seem necessary to me part of my job
incluso necesarias parte de mi trabajo
no but they would not put up with it they would not put up with anything they would not
no pero ellos no aguantarían no
put up with anything I mean imagine I
aguantarían nada no aguantarían nada o
imagine that they took
sea imaginaros yo me imagino que le le
out four or five accounts from each one
saquen a cada uno cuatro o cinco cuentas
like that mockingly with their names and they would not like
así de mofa con sus nombres y no les
their names on the
gustaría que pusieran sus nombres en las
accounts I do not know not a [ __ ] joke or a [ __ ]
cuentas no sé ni de [__] coña ni de [__]
joke be per fite you here of what he
coña sea per fite tú aquí de lo que me
has put me by Face I mean imagine
ha metido by de Face O sea imaginaros
this man in court eh in
este hombre en el juicio eh en los
court what does Javi have to do with it here already
juicio qué tiene que ver Javi aquí ya
that LL being a coward is already a brave
eso LL ser un [__] ya está un valiente
laser enjoy the lawsuits bro I do not know
láser disfruta las demandas bro no sé
what you want me to tell you he is
qué quieres que te diga él es un
brave enjoy Well if you are
valiente disfruta Pues si eres un
brave let's see if you take the let's see  if you
valiente a ver si coges el a ver si
take part in the lawsuit
coges y te personas tú en la demanda
laser len that you already have it eh It happens that
láser len que la tienes ya eh Pasa que
now apparently he has moved and now you do
ahora por lo visto se ha mudado y ahora
not take it either now he has moved
tampoco la coges ahora se ha mudado
now the player will have to see where he
ahora el jugado tendrá que ver a dónde
has moved I mean he keeps putting it off
se ha mudado O sea no para de alargarla
buddy Eh well I imagine that he will have to appear in
colega Eh bueno Me imagino que se tendrá
person at the Dallas prison and
que personar en la penal del Dallas y
there we will catch him you know or
por ahí lo trincar remos sabes o se la
Pablo will send it directly to
mandará Pablo directamente a la
his attorney or something because
procuradora suya o alguna cosa porque
come on I sued him since May
vamos ya hace que lo demandé desde mayo
and I am looking forward to the first one to pass Let him
y estoy deseando que pase la primera Que
answer the first one because I am going to
responda la primera porque le voy a
file a second one and Dallas too
poner una segunda y Dallas también
Dallas too I do not know if it is that it does not matter to him
Dallas también yo no sé si es que le da
if it is that he gets the defense for
igual si es que le sale la defensa
free or he considers that with these
gratis o él considera que con estas
explanations I do not know the truth are things
explicaci No lo sé la verdad son cosas
that I do not understand eh they are things that I do not
que no entiendo eh son cosas que no
understand no but there is a moment like I do not
entiendo no pero hay un momento como no
know if it is in the in the debate as if he
sé si es en el en el debate como que le
threw in uncle shur that
echó en cara al tío shur que el que el
uncle shur did not want did not want to be
tío shur no quería no quería ser
sued be something like that he threw in
demandado sea algo así le hecho en cara
uncle sh that uncle sh is
al tío sh que el tío sh se queda así
like Hello What is  what it was So the
como Hola Qué es lo que fue O sea que el
guy is defaming with full
tío está está difamando con pleno
knowledge eh I mean it's not a
conocimiento eh o sea con no es una
criticism of those in the discussion it's just that
crítica a los de la tertulia es solo que
the hate they're receiving is nothing
el hate que están recibiendo no es nada
Compared to what Javi receives no no no no no
Comparado a lo que Javi recibe no no no
[ __ ] way so it seems quite
ni [__] coña así que me parece bastante
absurd to me but well if a civil lawsuit makes him happy
absurdo pero bueno si le hace feliz una
go ahead tell me where it is man maybe
demanda civil adelante me dónde es tío a
Put reported not complaint start
lo mejor Pon denunciado no denuncia
wasting
meter a ser a perder el tiempo a
lawyers' time Ah I don't remember it was a
abogados a Ah no me acuerdo que fue
discussion that was like that eh You may also
tertulia que fue como eso eh Tú igual
be aware that you could eh
estás consciente de que podrías eh
receive a complaint for defamation or not I mean it
recibir una denuncia por difamación o no
depends on let's see because
O sea depende ya de a ver depende porque
if it is if it's not it's with a lot of contempt with
si es si no es con mucho desprecio con
Reckless contempt for the truth in theory
Temerario desprecio la verdad en teoría
no like that many people have been acquitted
no así he quedado absuelto mucha gente
then As long as he's there I think he's
entonces Mientras esté el Yo creo que es
an abuser and he's not an abuser
un maltratador y no es un maltratador
then we play it that way no no no no
entonces jugamos por ahí no no no no
but he said it with all his letters the
pero lo ha dicho con todas sus letras la
truth is that no no I don't like receiving
verdad es que no no me Mola recibir
complaints later not even that move bro
denuncias luego ni ni esa movida bro por
that's why I'm not going to tell you Dallas is a
eso yo no te voy a decir Dallas es un
groomer you know Of course  me neither you
groomer sabes Claro a mí tampoco a ti
neither you like it no it's that we are
tampoco te Mola no ya es que ahí estamos
all there that's the problem there there is the
todos ahí está la putada ahí ahí está la
question you know That's where you when
cuestión sabes Ahí es donde te cuando a
sometimes I talk about morals that says that I
veces hablo de moral que dice que yo
say that I am a moralist and I have said that I have
digo que soy moralista y yo he dicho que
never been a moralist in fact
nunca he sido moralista de hecho
I consider that being moral is a mistake
Considero que era moral es una un error
or rather everyone has it but
o sea todo el mundo la tiene pero
relying on morals seems repulsive to me
apoyarse en la moral me parece repulsivo
when you want to be right on that subject
cuando quieres tener razón con ese tema
but obviously we all have
pero obviamente todos tenemos principios
moral principles and unfortunately my
morales y por desgracia mis principios
moral principles and my ethics make it
morales y mi ética hacen que esté por
above telling the truth of what I believe
encima decir la verdad de lo que creo
above fear and the cage of
por encima del miedo y la cageta de de
a complaint that they can file against me when there are
una denuncia que me puedan poner cuando
sufficient indications what are you looking for I mean
hay indici suficientes qué busc O sea
what are you looking for do you think that Dallas and jav
qué buscas vos crees que Dallas y jav
oliveira will leave the internet that is your
oliveira se vayan de internet ese es tu
end let's see I don't remember but there was a
fin a ver no me acuerdo pero hubo un
moment that I'm not going to look for it because
momento que no lo voy a buscar porque
we're going to waste time but there was a
vamos a perder tiempo pero hubo un
moment like he said to
momento como que como que él le dijo al
uncle shur Ah pu what happens is that you
tío shur Ah pu que tú lo que pasa es que
don't want to receive a complaint and
no quieres recibir denuncia y le dice el
uncle sh says to him man of course I mean you can
tío sh hombre claro o sea tú puedes
expose and you can say everything you
exponer y puedes decir todo lo que tú
want without  defame Of course of course I mean it's not
quieras sin difamar Claro claro o sea no
or what he wants to normalize
es o sea lo que él quiere normalizar
but only when it's him who is being
pero solo cuando es a él al que se la
sued Okay when are we the others maybe the ones who are being
ponen Vale cuando somos los demás a lo
sued for
mejor a los que nos demandan por
insulting or for I don't know what okay it's for
insultar o por no sé qué vale que es por
expressions that are very different I mean
expresiones que es muy diferente o sea
a lawsuit for the right to honor could
una demanda por derecho a honor puede
be for insults I mean have you seen what
ser por insultos O sea ya visteis lo que
the lawsuits that they've put on me are like
son las demandas que me han puesto a mí
hair broom I don't know what or the one from Nauter No the one they
pelo escoba no sé qué o la de nauter No
put on Nauter [ __ ] eh
la que le pusieron a nauter cabronazo eh
[ __ ] I don't know what you know no no no very
[__] No sé qué sabes no no no muy
different is what you say every day
diferente es lo que tú dices cada día
my son very very very different that if
hijo mío muy muy muy diferente que si
abuser that if groomer that if I don't know
maltratador que si groomer que si no sé
or rather very different you understand me and and he
o sea muy diferente me entiendes y y él
wants to normalize how eh Like it's not that that
quiere normalizar cóm que eh Como que no
's the price for telling the
es que eso es el precio por decir la
truth like what what I mean I really I mean I don't
verdad como qué qué O sea yo de verdad O
understand eh I don't understand
sea no lo entiendo eh No lo entiendo
because he has already signed that he is
porque ya él como que ha firmado que lo
going to continue doing it and that and that he doesn't care about
va a seguir haciendo y que y que le da
the lawsuit and all the r that's okay
igual la demanda y todo el r ese vale
So nothing you keep going with those
Así que nada tú sigue con esas
expressions every  days and we're
expresiones todos los días y nosotros
going to sue you every day I mean if there are
todos los días te vamos a demandar O sea
no evils we don't have a
si es que no hay mals tampoco tenemos un
lawyer there who doesn't have it already done, let's say he's
abogado ahí que que no tiene ya hecho
missing the flat rate no
vamos le falta ya la tarifa plana no
Karime but it's not even that well
Karime pero es que ni siquiera es eso
you could express yourself in another
pues tú te podrías expresar de otra
way when you think that I don't know
manera a la hora tú piensas que no sé
who's right Well then you can
quién tiene razón Bueno pues tú puedes
express it in a way that doesn't violate
expresarlo de manera que no vulnes el
people's honor you know but well level
honor de la gente sabes pero bueno nivel
This is okay I don't know who the [ __ ]
Este vale No sé quién [__] es el
Chris Chan is but I'm sure Dallas is
Chris Chan ese pero seguro que Dallas es
worse And that's it if you want to find out about
peor Y ya está si te quieres informar de
that Tommy Black has a very
eso Tommy Black tiene un vídeo muy
complete video about Chris Chan well I'll watch it I'll
completo sobre Chris Chan pues lo veré
watch it if it makes you want I'll read you
lo veré si te hace ilusión yo te leo
but then Chris Chan is a crazy guy
pero entonces chis Chan es un loquito
Chris Chan is a crazy guy and a
Chris Chan es un loquito y un
criminal because he was in prison I'm
delincuente porque él estuvo preso me
glad so you don't criticize Dallas
alegro entonces tú no criticas a Dallas
because Cristian is worse because I
porque Cristian es peor porque te
remind you that that was your point and the
recuerdo que ese fue tu punto y las
evidence Mr. Laser if you want I put
pruebas señor laser si quieres Pongo
here everything that Dala has done and you
aquí todo lo que ha hecho dala y tú le
call him crazy Haha man It's that this
llamas loquito Jaja tío Es que este
man has a lawsuit and a complaint
hombre tiene una demanda y una denuncia
and he's here saying that a guy who has
y está aquí diciendo que un tío que ha
done what what things has
hecho lo que qué cosas ha hecho el
Christian done  this one is in jail no
chistian este ese está en la cárcel no
What things did Chis's father do along
Qué cosas hizo el padre de chis junto
with Barbara are the victims of this
con Bárbara son las víctimas de esta
story he threatened to kill a boy in
historia amenazó de muerte un chico en
his hand because they won a contest I
su mano porque ganaron un concurso yo
criticize Dala whenever he does something wrong
critico a dala siempre que hace algo mal
the day he goes to jail I'm going to say that he
el día que caiga preso voy a decir que
's a criminal like I say with Crisan
es un delincuente como digo con crisan
until then a
hasta entonces me va a aparecer un
sick guy like everyone else is going to appear to me and say laser well he
enfermito como todos y dice láser pues
can call him a criminal yes yes I mean
ya puede llamarle delincuente si si o
man that guy is being sued Eh
sea tío que ese pavo está demandado Eh
well you can call him a criminal if you
pues ya puedes llamarle delincuente si
want because failing to comply with a sentence
quiere porque incumplir una sentencia
of the supreme court is a crime point
del tribunal supremo Es delito punto
number one I mean you know eh if he
número uno o sea Tú qué sabes eh si lo
fails to comply or not he fails to comply with the deadlines that there are I mean
incumple o no lo incumple los plazos que
an
hay o sea se tendrá que pedir una
execution will have to be requested and they will have to report him
ejecución y y tendrán que denunciarlo
they will have to condemn him not a thousand things but
tendrán que condenarlo no mil cosas pero
now an execution has to be carried out And
ahora se tiene que hacer una ejecución Y
then deadlines are given but no no
entonces se dan unos plazos pero no no
he takes it for granted that well okay I already do
él da por hecho que bueno vale Ya lo
today you will also call
hago hoy tú también llamarás delincuente
people who have a sentence for
a la gente que tiene una condena por
something and do not serve it criminals of course who is I don't
algo y no la cumple claro quién es no te
remember anything from 2017 about a dog that
recuerd nada de 2017 de un perrito que
disappeared out of nowhere car  I'm not
desapareció de la nada coche que yo no
asking you if it's okay or not to
te estoy preguntando si está bien o no
comply Estefanía a kiss I mean you
el cumplir Estefanía un beso o sea
want me to talk about a sentence from 2017 that is
quieres que hable una sentencia de 2017
8 years ago of the one that says that
o sea de hace 8 años de la que dice que
laser with us weight short hair and
laser con nos peso corto de pelo y
bathed is Javi Javi from 2000 what André
bañado es Javi Javi del 2000 qué André
please Don't [ __ ] with him he says I mean you want me to
por favor No jodas dice o sea quieres
talk about a sentence from 2017 that is
que hable de una sentencia de 2017 o sea
8 years ago Ah well you can't
de hace 8 años Ah bueno no se puede
talk about things from 8 years ago okay about the one they
hablar de cosas de hace 8 años vale de
say they say that the dog got
la que dicen dicen que el perro se
lost and there's nothing firm yet It's
perdió y aún no hay nada en firme Es
weird no but that sentence was not carried out
raro no pero esa sentencia no se cumplió
no they didn't return the dog no And what's
no no devolvieron al perro no Y eso que
relevant about that if there's no
tiene de relevante si no hay una
firm sentence that is And even if it is
sentencia en firme que se Y aunque esté
firm We'll have to wait for
en firme Tendremos que esperar a que
someone to go to jail nothing no no no it's that
alguien vaya a la cárcel que nada no no
this I don't know it doesn't make sense
no es que esto yo no sé no tiene sentido
look at this Dallas got on a 15
mirar este Dallas se subió a una de 15
year old in a hotel he hit his dog he
años a un hotel le pegaba a su perro
killed his Chameleon he
mató a su Camaleón maltrataba
psychologically abused Miare I mean this is what they're
psicológicamente a miare o sea esto es
going to condemn him It's that this one you're
que lo van a condenar Es que este tu
going to condemn dude  this is
solo ya lo van a condenar tío esto es
a condemnation this you alone scammed hundreds
una condena este tu solo estafó cientos
of thousands of euros from his followers I was
de miles de euros a sus seguidores me
wrong Tommy didn't dedicate a single
equivoqué Tommy no le dedicó un solo
video to him he dedicated two parts It's that
víde le dedicó dos partes Es que lo de
Christian Estela saying that Dallas is
Christian Estela decir que Dallas es
worse is crazy I don't know the truth I mean they
peor es una locura no sé la verdad O sea
want to censor him eh he says dude what's
lo quieren censurar eh dice tío que qué
not to say Well they're going to sue him No
no es decir Bueno lo van a demandar No
no it's that he's being sued he says I'll play and
no es que está demandado dice tocaré y
even so he doesn't have the balls to
aún así no hay huevo de decirle
directly call him groomer because of the no no the
directamente groomer por lo de no no el
groomer has told him in several
groomer sí le ha dicho en en varias
parts of the lawsuit there's the thing about gromer he called him
partes de la demanda hay lo de gromer le
pedophile he told him a lot
ha dicho pedófilo le ha dicho un montón
of things I really I mean I don't
de cosas yo de verdad O sea no lo
understand eh I don't understand look I
entiendo eh No lo entiendo mira que yo
was a camicas eh a long time ago eh
era camicas eh hace un montón de años eh
look I was a camicas but that's already
mira que yo era camicas pero eso ya es
that he is being sued already eh I don't know
que lo sea estando ya demandado eh No sé
dude it seems too much even for him I
tío me parece demasiado incluso para él
don't know if he's thinking of leaving the country if he has
no sé si es que se piensa ir del país si
left the country I don't know the truth I don't
se ha ido del país No lo sé la verdad no
know I don't know I'm trying to make
sé No lo sé No lo sé intento en una
sense of why someone would act like that
lógica de Por qué alguien actuaría así
but I don't know you're talking about Education look at yourself
pero no lo sé hablas de Educación mírate
How  you talk to others Pablo This other one
Cómo hablas a los demás Pablo Este otro
not exposing criminals eh and da Alis
no exponiendo criminales eh y da alis
Veira says You know this year is your
veira dice Tú sabes que este año es tu
lucky day we already have evidence of
día de suerte ya tenemos evidencia de
how you bribed judges so
cómo sobornaste a jueces para que gane
Dallas would win And Javi No, it's not that neither I in my
Dallas Y Javi No no es que ni yo en mi
time or rather I in my time hater in
época o sea ni yo en mi época hater en
my time that I was crazy that I had no
mi época que se me iba la olla que no
control I didn't even know that
controlaba no sabía que existían ni
lawsuits existed eh I mean I did
siquiera las demandas eh o sea yo eso sí
see that there was civil criminal law that you
vi eso de que existía civil penal eso de
could sue for insults and
que se podía demandar por insultos y
all that I didn't know that it existed I
demás yo no sabía que existía Yo me
remember that a guy once insulted a
acuerdo que un sino una vez insultó a un
doctor I don't remember how angry he got
médico no me acuerdo que cabreo se cogió
with a doctor in a consultation and the
con un médico en una consulta y el
doctor insulted him and no the doctor reported him and
médico lo insultó y no el médico lo
paid him he had to pay him 50
denunció y le pagó le tuvo que pagar 50
or something like that I don't remember what it was anyway I
o algo así no me acuerdo que fue sea yo
remember that people have been reported here
me acuerdo que aquí se ha denunciado
for insults in the past and and it seems like it
gente por insulto antiguamente y y como
never came to anything I don't know what you
que no llegaba a nada nunca no sé qué
know I had that trial with the
sabes tuve el juicio aquel con el
crazy guy here who told me that I'm going to
loquito aqu que me dijo lo de te voy a
split you in half Do you remember
partir por la mitad Te acuerdas
failing to comply with a sentence for  insults is
incumplir una sentencia por insultos es
a serious crime so nothing Dallas we
un delito grave pues nada Dallas te
will have to send you to the cecot with in El
Tendremos que mandar al cecot con en El
Salvador serious or not serious It is something
Salvador grave ni no grave Es una cosa
that cannot be done you cannot
que no no se puede hacer no se puede
violate a sentence and I do not count
incumplir una sentencia y yo no cuento
I hope that d is not going to cross his
Espero que d no se le vaya a pasar por
mind let's go me for the times that I
la cabeza vamos yo por las veces que yo
have spoken with him about this subject at
he hablado con él de ese tema a mí en
no time has he urged me not to
ningún momento me ha insado de que no lo
pay it will he pay it will put the four
vaya a pagar lo pagará pondrá las cuatro
screenshots of the sentence, that is to say the ruling
capturas de la sentencia o sea el fallo
in four videos Random and out he is not going to
en cuatro vídeos Random y fuera no va a
No not to comply with a sentence those who
No a no cumplir una sentencia los que
have violated a sentence are the
han incumplido una sentencia son los
others no But it is that no no no that it does not
otros no Pero es que no no no que da
matter that it does not matter
igual que da
i
igual i
[Music]
[Música]